

Audio visual professional living in Amsterdam. I've been freelancing in the creative industry since 2006. My main focus and expertise is video editing and production of video content. Primarly editing TV commercials, mood films, brand films and diverse audio visual content. I've collaborated with Heineken, Nike, adidas, TomTom, Ikea and brands alike. I've enjoyed producing films for prestigious cultural award ceremonies like the Erasmus Prize.

## experience

# Kettu Bisnis Productions september 2006 - present

Providing full range of services in video production for commercial clients and the cultural sector. Overseeing all aspects of production work including financial, creative, and technical processes.

http://kettubisnis.com/

## XXS Amsterdam June 2013 - present

Working as creative video editor independently and together with the agency creatives and producers. Managing, producing and directing projects besides editing. https://www.xxs.amsterdam/

## Amsterdam Worldwide September 2006 -present

Working as creative video editor closely together with the agency creatives. Managing and producing projects as well. https://www.amsterdamworldwide.com/

#### 180 Amsterdam June 2005 - September 2006

Worked in the hectic in-house video editing facility with brands like adidas, Amstel, Opel, Motorola etc. http://180amsterdam.com/

## 50 FPS (now Filmmore) September 2003 - April 2005

Worked as video editor and DVD designer in post production company for clients like A-film - the largest distributor of films in the Benelux.

http://filmmore.nl/en/home

#### Provideo / Generator Post Helsinki | Aug 2000 - Dec 2002

Worked as video editor and DVD designer in full service post production company in Helsinki.

#### skills and software

Great in choosing strong visuals to help client tell their story the best possible way. Good people skills. Fast worker. Great understanding of brand identities and corporate communications.

Adobe CC: Premiere Pro, After Effects, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign.

## education

Tampere polytechnic of Art and Media 1996 - 2000

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Multimedia production.